http://www.thorvertonstone.co.uk/privacy-policy

HomeAbout UsAwardsProductsWindow SurroundsCoping StonesPier CapsWindow CillsPorticosQuoin StonesHeadsDoor SurroundsBalustradingStepsGarden SculpturesPearBig AppleWalnutBig FootAcornsDaffodil PlaqueTriton MaskFrench henOwlMore ProductsBand CourseCorbelsJambs & MullionsName & Date StonesColumns and PilastersFireplacesColour ChartDownloadsTechnicalDelivery OptionsPointing Mix InstructionsGarden SculpturesPearBig AppleWalnutBig FootAcornTriton MaskFrench henOwlMemorial4 inch foundationsAshlar SetsChamfered / Pencil Edge BasesSolid LandingsCremation BasesFrame LandingsMoulded Edge FoundationsMiscellaneousContact UsOrder BrochureGallery
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information.
The following outlines our privacy policy.
We are Thorverton Stone Company Ltd, a company incorporated in England and Wales. Our Company No. is 3530364, our registered address is Seychelles Farm, Upton Pyne, Exeter, EX5 5HY.
We are committed to ensuring your privacy is protected and comply with the General Data Protection Regulation. We are the controller of the data that you pass to us.
This privacy policy sets out how we collect personal information from you and how the personal information that you provide will be processed by us. By visiting our website, contacting us through social media, emailing or telephoning us you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy. If you do not consent please do not submit any data to us.
What information do we hold and how do we use it.
We may collect and process the following data about you:
You may give us information about you by filling in our enquiry form or our order brochure form on our website or corresponding with us by telephone, social media, email or in writing. This information may include your name, title, email address, IP address, location and telephone number. We will retain this information whilst we are corresponding with you or fulfilling an order you have placed with us and meeting legal requirements.
Cookies
The website uses performance cookies to collect information about how visitors use our website, for instance, which pages are visited most often. These cookies do not collect information that identifies a visitor. Data collected is aggregated therefore anonymous.
How we use the information
To carry out our obligations arising from any contract we have entered into with you and to provide you with information, products and services you have requested.
We process personal information for certain legitimate business purposes:
To maintain our own accounts and records in order to meet legal requirements.
To identify and prevent fraud
To enhance the security of our network and information systems.
To better understand how people interact with our websites
To administer our website.
You have the right to withdraw your consent to processing of your personal data at any time.
Third Party sites
Our site may contain a link to third party websites including websites for purchasing products. They are provided for your convenience only, we have no responsibility for the content of these linked websites.
Where your data is stored
Your information is stored on password protected computers and our secure servers and backed up to a secure backup. Associated paperwork is stored in lockable cabinets within an onsite lockable office.
How safe is your information
Protecting your privacy is important to us. The website is protected by various levels of secure technology which are designed to protect your information from unauthorised or unlawful access. Any payment transactions will be encrypted (using SSL technology) payments are taken through Sage pay gateway and no card details are stored locally.
We will do our best to protect your personal data but the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Any such transmission is therefore at your own risk.
Data Retention
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including the purposes of satisfying any legal or accounting or reporting requirements. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use of or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means and the applicable legal requirements.
Disclosure of your information
We may share your information with selected third parties:
Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the fulfilment of any contract we enter into with you.
We may disclose your personal information where we:
Need to disclose it to protect our rights, property or safety of our customers including the exchange of information with other companies organisations or government bodies for the purpose of fraud  protection and credit risk reduction.
Are under a legal duty to comply with any legal obligation or in order to enforce our terms and conditions
Sell our business or assets in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective buyer.
We do not transfer your personal data outside the European Economic Area.
We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.
Your rights in respect of your data
If your information changes let us know so that we make the necessary changes to the information we hold for you. If you wish to see the information we hold on you we will process your request free of charge. If you wish for your information to be deleted or if you have any complaints about our use of your personal data:
Please contact the data manager on caststone@thorvertonstone.co.uk or by writing to the above registered address.
If this does not resolve your complaint to your satisfaction you have a right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office on 03031231113 or via email https:/ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/ or at Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow SK9 5AF, England.
